Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Production, Art and Design, Photographs and Negatives, Office Files of Laura Walworth and Dayna Bealy FA1819
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Production, Art and Design, Photographs and Negatives, Office Files of Laura Walworth and Dayna Bealy
1993-2001
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
Walworth, Laura
Bealy, Dayna
FA1819
12.9 Cubic Feet 31 containers
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in two series:
1.) Office Files of Laura Walworth, 1993-2001
2.) Office Files of Dayna Bealy, 1997-2000
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred to RAC in 2017 by the Ford Foundation and ingested by RAC as Accession 2017:093.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains photographs of grantees' activities used by the Ford Foundation for various publications, including annual reports, fall reports, winter reports, and Innovations in State and Local Government materials. The folder title typically indicates a Ford identification number, the name of the grantee or event photographed, the publication the photographs were intended for, the Ford Foundation unit responsible for the grant (for examples: Peace and Social Justice PSJ or Governance and Civil Society GCS), and the name of the photographer.
Photographs
- Office Files of Laura Walworth, 1993-2001; 1; 4.27 Cubic Feet 11 containers
  - 1020 - Dia de Los Muertos, Museo Chicano in Phoenix, Jeffry D. Scott, photographer, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Six 8x10 black and white prints, one contact sheet
  - 1021 - Annual Report 1995, Société Africaine d'Education et de Formation pour le Développement (SAFEFOD), Governance and Public Policy, Abdoul Aziz Bathily, photographer (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Four 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1023 - Annual Report 1995, High School, Education and Culture, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    17 black and white 8x10 prints, six contact sheets
  - 1024 - Annual Report 1995, Henry Louis Gates, Jr. and Cornel West, Du Bois Institute Colloquia, Education and Culture, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    10 8x10 black and white prints, four contact sheets
  - 1025 - Annual Report 1995, UNCF Conference at LeMoyne-Owen College, Education and Culture - Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    10 8x10 black and white prints, 4 contact sheets
  - 1026 - Annual Report 1995, Alabama Southern Community College Forestry Students, Education and Culture - Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    16 8x10 black and white photographs, 7 contact sheets
  - Annual Report 1995, Council on Foreign Relations Cold War Studies Program (Box 1, Folder 7)
    One black and white 8x10 print
  - 1028 - Winter Report 1997, Atlanta Neighborhood Development (ANDP), Historic District Development Corporation (HDDC), Rob Amberg, photographer, 1996 April (Box 1, Folder 8)
    19 8x10 black and white prints, 22 contact sheets
  - 1029 - Summer/Fall 1996, Barbara Williams Lewis, Minority Doctoral Fellow Graduating from USC, Education and Culture, Slobodan Dimitrov (Box 1, Folder 9)
    4 8x10 black and white prints, 3 contact sheets
  - 1030 - Winter 1997, Del Valley Community Investment Fund - Nehemiah West Houses, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania and North Camden, New Jersey, PRI, David H. Wells, photographer, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    19 8x10 black and white prints, 19 8x10 contact sheets
  - 1031 - Navajo Nation Teacher Prep at Fort Lewis-Durango, Colorado, S/F, Education and Culture, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    13 black and white prints, 22 contact sheets
  - 1032 - Second Chance Teachers Program at Clark Atlanta University, Atlanta, S/F, Education and Culture, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    12 8x10 prints and six contact sheets
  - 1033 - RCCI at Southwest Texas Junior College, Uvalde, Texas, S/F, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    12 8x10 black and white prints, six contact sheets
  - 1034 - NCAS (School Reform), San Antonio, Texas, S/F, Education and Culture, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    12 8x10 black and white prints, 8 contact sheets
  - 1035 - NYC School Reform Roundtable Discussion at Ford Foundation, Education and Culture, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1996 May (Box 2, Folder 15)
    6 8x10 black and white prints, 1 contact sheet
  - 1036 - Community Development Collaborative Partnership Conference, Raleigh, North Carolina UP, Jennifer Warburgh, photographer, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    4 8x10 black and white prints, 14 contact sheets
  - 1037 - Winter Report 1997, Center for Community Self-Help, PRI, Jennifer Warburg, photographer, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17-18, Box 3, Folder 19)
    23 8x10 black and white prints, 4 3.5x5 black and white prints, 32 contact sheets
  - 1038 - Annual Report 1996, Northwest Asian American Theater, Seattle, Education and Culture, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer (Box 3, Folder 20)
    13 8x10 black and white prints, 7 contact sheets
  - 1039 - Annual Report 1996, Parents for Public Schools, Jackson, Mississippi, Education and Culture, Jeffry Henson Scales, photographer, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    30 8x10 black and white photographs, 2 contact sheets
  - 1040 - Reaching Common Ground: A Day of Dialogue, Low Income Families, Urban Poverty, Maria Melin, photographer, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
    4 black and white contact sheets
  - 1041 - Inland Fisheries, Bangladesh, Cindy Andrew, photographer, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    40 slides, 8 8.5x11 black and white photocopies
  - 1042-A - 1996 Innovations, Arts Incubator, Arlington County, Virginia (Box 3, Folder 25)
    9 8x10 black and white photos, 8 contact sheets
  - 1042-B - 1996 Innovations, California Environmental Technical Certification (Box 3, Folder 26)
    7 8x10 black and white prints, 6 contact sheets
  - 1042-C - 1996 Innovations, Compstat: A Crime Reduction Management Tool (Box 3, Folder 27)
    7 8x10 black and white prints, 5 contact sheets
  - 1042-D - 1996 Innovations, Consequence Assessment Tool Set and Operations Cost (Box 4, Folder 28)
    9 8x10 black and white prints, 4 contact sheets
  - 1042-E - 1996 Innovations, Consolidated Planning/Community Connections HUD (Box 4, Folder 29)
    6 8x10 black and white prints, 5 contact sheets
  - 1042-F - 1996 Innovations, Eradicating Sweat Shops, Department of Labor (Box 4, Folder 30)
    7 8x10 black and white prints, 2 contact sheets
  - 1042-G - 1996 Innovations, Florida Healthy Kids Program, State of Florida (Box 4, Folder 31)
    6 8x10 prints, 6 contact sheets
  - 1042-H - 1996 Innovations, Greater Avenues for Independence (GAIN), Riverside County, California (Box 4, Folder 32)
    6 8x10 black and white prints, 6 contact sheets
  - 1996 Innovations, Photo Log and Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 1042-I - 1996 Innovations, Oregon Health Plan, State of Oregon (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 1042-J - 1996 Innovations, Santa Fe Affordable Housing Roundtable, City of Santa Fe (Box 4, Folder 35)
    10 8x10 black and white prints, 9 contact sheets
  - 1043 - 1996 Annual Report, Trust Fund, Morogoro, Tanzania, Reproductive Health and Population, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 4, Folder 36)
    9 8x10 black and white prints, 6 black and white contact sheets
  - 1044 - 1996 Annual Report, Kenya Association of Professional Counselors, Kenya, Reproductive Health and Population, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 4, Folder 37)
    2 8x10 black and white prints, 2 contact sheets, 2 sets of negatives
  - 1045 - 1996 Annual Report, Environmental Liaison Center, E. Africa, Reproductive Health and Population, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 4, Folder 38)
    6 8x10 black and white prints, 4 cpntact sheets
  - 1046 - 1996 Annual Report, Aga Khan Foundation, Kenya, Urban Poverty, Reproductive Health and Population, and Education and Culture, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 4, Folder 39)
    5 8x10 black and white prints, 5 contact sheets, one envelope of negatives
  - 1047 - 1996 Annual Report, National Cooperative Housing Union, Kenya, Urban Poverty, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 4, Folder 40)
    8 8x10 black and white prints, 4 contact sheets
  - Correspondence and Press Release - Wing Huie Working Capital Fund for Minority Cultural Institutions, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 1051 - 1994 Annual Report, The Pratt Institute, Recent Grants PRI (Box 5, Folder 42)
    8 4x6 prints, 12 5x7 prints
  - 1052 - 1994 Annual Report, Enterprise Foundation, Columbia, Maryland, Recent Grants PRI (Box 5, Folder 43)
    2 sets of black and white negatives, 2 black and white contact sheets, 3 black and white 8x10 prints, 30 4x6 color prints
  - 1052 - 1994 Annual Report, Enterprise Foundation, Columbia, Maryland, Recent Grants PRI - negatives (Box 27, Folder 326)
    2 sets of black and white negatives
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Preservation Concerns
  - 1053 - 1994 Annual Report, National Federation of Community Development Credit Unions, Brooklyn, New York, Recent Grants PRI (Box 5, Folder 44)
    3 8x10 black and white prints, 2 4x6 color prints
  - 1054 - 1994 Annual Report, SEEDCO, Recent Grants PRI (Box 5, Folder 45)
    one black and white contact sheet, 2 5x7 black and white prints, 1 4x6 color print
  - 1054 - 1994 Annual Report, Mobilization Against Desertification, Kenya, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 5, Folder 46)
    9 8x10 black and white prints,3 black and white contact sheets
  - 1054 - 1994 Annual Report, Mobilization Against Desertification, Kenya, Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 327)
    3 sets of negatives
  - 1055 - 1994 Annual Report, BRAC Bank Bangladesh (Box 5, Folder 47)
    10 4x6 color prints
  - 1056 - Winter Report 1997, Zuni Pueblo, Tony O'Brien, photographer (Box 5, Folder 48)
    5 8x10 black and white prints, 8 black and white contact sheets
  - 1056 - Winter Report 1997, Zuni Pueblo, Tony O'Brien, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 328)
    7 sheets of black and white negatives
  - 1057 - Winter Report 1997, Bobbi Guttman, Motorola VP for Global Diversity, R. G. Marc PoKempner, photographer (Box 5, Folder 49)
    6 black and white contact sheets, 14 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1058 - Working Capital Fund for Minority Cultural Institution, Education and Culture, Wing Young Huie, photographer, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    9 black and white contact sheets
  - 1058 - Working Capital Fund for Minority Cultural Institution, Education and Culture, Wing Young Huie, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 329)
    9 sheets of negatives
  - 1059 - Inroads/Africa Conference, "African Art and the Making of History," Education and Culture, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1996 June (Box 6, Folder 51-52)
    70 8x10 black and white sheets
  - 1062 - Annual Report 1994, New Community Corporation, New Jersey, Lauran Compren, photographer (Box 6, Folder 53)
    3 5x7 black and white prints, 1 color print
  - 1063 - 1994 Annual Report, The Pratt Institute Access Houses, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1994 August (Box 6, Folder 54)
    7 black and white contact sheets
  - 1064 - 1994 Annual Report, Action Housing, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1994 August (Box 6, Folder 55)
    5 black and white contact sheets
  - 1065 - 1994 Annual Report, Atlanta Neighborhood Development Partnership, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1994 August (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 1066 - 1994 Annual Report, Chicanos Por La Causa, Stephen Shames, photographer (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - 1067 - Community College of Denver, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    6 black and white contact sheets
  - 1068 - Drew Child Development Corporation, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - 1069 - 1994 Annual Report, Housing Our Families, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1994 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    10 black and white contact sheets
  - 1070 - 1994 Annual Report, Jobs for the Future, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1994 July 25 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    1 8x10 black and white print, 7 black and white contact sheets
  - 1071 - 1994 Annual Report, National Association of Childcare Resource and Referral Agencies, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1994 August 13 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - 1072 - 1996 Annual Report, National Economic Development and Law Center, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1996 July 19 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - 1073 - 1994 Annual Report, Northwest Corridor/CDC, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1994 September 1 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    3 black and white contact sheets
  - 1074 - 1994 Annual Report, YMCA, Stephen Shames, photographer, 1994 September 1 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    5 8x10 black and white prints, 13 black and white contact sheets
  - 997-PA - Winter Report 1996, Shoot A, Alex Kirkbride, photographer, 1995 October (Box 7, Folder 66)
    4 5x7 black and white prints, 4 contact sheets
  - 997-PA - Annual Report 1995, Shoot B, Tom Sobolik, photographer (Box 7, Folder 67)
    5 black and white 8x10 prints, 2 contact sheets
  - 998 - Annual Report 1995, Center for Population and Family Health, Columbia, Janette Beckman, photographer (Box 7, Folder 68)
    4 black and white 8x10 photos, 7 contact sheets
  - 999-4 - Annual Report 1995, Women Lawyers, Walter Calahan, photographer (Box 7, Folder 69)
    1 contact sheet, 3 8x10 photos
  - 999-4 - Annual Report 1995, Women Lawyers, Walter Calahan, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 330)
    4 negative strips
  - 1000 - Annual Report 1995, Door, Mark Asnin/Saba (Box 7, Folder 70)
    9 8x10 prints, 19 contact sheets
  - 1000 - Annual Report 1995, Door, Mark Asnin/Saba - negatives (Box 27, Folder 331)
    19 negative strips
  - 1001 - Annual Report 1995, SEEDCO, William Durante, photographer (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - 1001 - Spring 1996, SEEDCO, William Durante, photographer (Box 7, Folder 72)
    3 8x10 black and white prints, 2 contact sheets
  - 1001 -Spring 1996, SEEDCO, William Durante, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 332)
    4 strips of negatives
  - 1002 - Spring 1996, MES/ARTS Students, Bard College, Education and Culture, Antonio Gonzalez, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    14 black and white 8x10 prints, 6 contact sheets
  - I Want to Remember He Wants to Forget, Producer and Director: Eitan Oren, NTSC, 1997; 62 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13071)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - 1003 - Spring Report 1996, United Cambodian Community Center, Long Beach, California, Ann Summa, photographer (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - 1004 - Fall Report 1996, Second Chance Teachers, Military to Schools, Rob Amberg, photographer (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - 1005 - Annual Report 1995, ShoreBank, Kevin Horan, photographer (Box 8, Folder 76)
    7 8x10 black and white prints, 10 contact sheets
  - 1005 - Annual Report 1995, Kevin Horan, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 333)
    11 sets of negatives
  - 1006 - Annual Report 1995, The Desert Is No Lady, Jeffry Scott, photographer (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - 1007 - National Council of La Raza, Housing America, Yuma, Arizona, Jeffry Scott, photographer - negatives, 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 78)
    3 copies of negative strips
  - 1008 - 1995 Annual Report, Maya Angelou Urban Renewal Project, The Empowerment Network Conference, Portland, Oregon, Kristin Finnegan, 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 79)
    3 8x10 black and white prints, 4 contact sheets
  - 1008 - 1995 Annual Report, Maya Angelou Urban Renewal Project, The Empowerment Network Conference, Portland, Oregon, Kristin Finnegan - negatives, 1995 October (Box 27, Folder 334)
    5 strips of negatives
  - 1009 - 1995 Annual Report, Moorehouse Research, Urban Poverty, Rob Amberg, photographer (Box 8, Folder 80)
    8 black and white 8x10 photos, 10 contact sheets
  - 1010 - Annual Report 1995, MCG/New Community, Andrew Lichtenstein, photographer (Box 8, Folder 81)
    7 black and white prints, 14 contact sheets
  - 1010 - Annual Report 1995, MCG/New Community, Andrew Lichtenstein, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 335)
    Restricted - preservation concerns
  - 1011 - Annual Report 1995, MVCDC, Barbara Nitke, photographer (Box 8, Folder 82)
    4 contact sheets
  - 1012 - Annual Report 1995, University of Toronto Conference, Dante Busquetes-Sordo, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - 1013 - Annual Report 1995, Peacemakers Graduation, Andrew Lichtenstein, photographer (Box 8, Folder 84)
    7 8x10 black and white photos, 3 contact sheets
  - 1014 - Annual Report 1995, National Headstart, Piet van Lier, photographer (Box 8, Folder 85)
    9 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1015 - Annual Report 1995, Asian Neighborhood Design, Mark Richards, photographer (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - 1015 - Annual Report 1995, Asian Neighborhood Design, Mark Richards, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 336)
    6 negative strips
  - 1016 - Spring Report 1996, Brooklyn/Central Brooklyn Credit Union, Jeffrey Hanson Scales, photographer (Box 9, Folder 87)
    9 8x10 prints, 8 contact sheets
  - 1017 - Annual Report 1996/AVANCE, Spring Report 1996, Pursuing the Dream, Stephen Shames, photographer (Box 9, Folder 88)
    3 8x10 black and white photos
  - 1018 - Spring Report 1996, Portrait of Stephen Shames, David H. Wells, photographer (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - 1019 - 1996 Spring Report, Ernesto Cortes, Jr., Jana Birchum, photographer (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - 1020 - Headshot of Susan V. Berresford, President Ford Foundation, Ben Russell, photographer, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    1 black and white photo
  - Three Certificates of Training Seminars for Margaret Howard for Windows 3.1 and Lans, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Working File - Press Clippings, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Timeline/Stats, 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Annual Report 1995, Recommendations for Grant/FAP Action Forms, Photos by Antonio Gonzalez, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - A Piece of Cloth, 1993 February; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13072)
  - ESMA: El Dia del Juicio, Un documental de Magdalena Ruiz Guiñazú, undated; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13073)
- Office Files of Dayna Bealy, 1997-2000; 2; 9.4 Cubic Feet 22 containers
  - 1126 - Bay Area Institute, San Francisco, California, EMAC, Education, Knowledge, and Religion, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1997 April 20-23 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    12 contact sheets, 15 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1127 - Campus Diversity, Public Info Project (Edgar Beckham), EMAC, Education, Knowledge, Religion, Antonio Gonzalez, photographer, 1997 June 18 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    5 contact sheets, 13 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1128 - Miami Dade Community College's Department of Cultural Affairs, Center for Cultural Collaborations International, EMAC, Culture, Arts, Media, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    13 5x7 black and white prints
  - 1129 - UCLA Center for Intercultural Performance, Asia Pacific Performance Exchange Program, EMAC, Culture, Arts, Media, Marvin Inouye and Carol Peterson, photographers, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    1 contact sheet, 16 8x10 black and white prints, 4 5x7 black and white prints
  - 1130 - National Arts Stabilization, EMAC, Culture, Arts, Media, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    4 5x7 black and white prints
  - 1131 - Institute of International Education (Six Theatre/Arts/Dance Groups), Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Culture, Arts, Media, undated (Box 10, Folder 101)
    5 5x7 color photos, 8 5x7 black and white photos
  - 1132A - Innovations 1997, "Disarming the Criminal," US Department of the Treasury, Bureau of Alcohol, Firearms, and Tobacco, Earl Dotter, 1997 September 12 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    2 contact sheets, 1 8x10 black and white print
  - 1132A - Innovations 1997, "Disarming the Criminal," US Department of the Treasury, Bureau of Alcohol, Firearms, and Tobacco, Earl Dotter - negatives, 1997 September 12 (Box 27, Folder 337)
    2 sets of negatives
  - 1132B - Innovations 1997, Healthy Start, State of Hawaii, David Current, photographer, 1997 September 12 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    9 contact sheets, 6 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1132C - Innovations 1997, Decategorized Human Services Delivery, Tioga County, Pennsylvania, Stella Johnson, photographer, 1997 September 14 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    10 contact sheets, 5 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1132D - Innovations 1997, Operation Cease Fire, Boston Police Department, City of Boston, Stella Johnson, photographer, 1997 September 19 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    14 contact sheets, 4 8x10 black and white prints, 6 5x7 black and white prints
  - 1132E - Innovations 1997, IRS Telefile, US Treasury, Rob Emberg, photographer (Box 10, Folder 106)
    6 contact sheets, 6 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1132F - Innovations 1997, State of Georgia, Office of School Readiness, Voluntary Pre-Kindergarten Program, Rob Amberg, photographer (Box 10, Folder 107)
    6 contact sheets, 2 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1132G - Innovations 1997, State of North Carolina, North Carolina Sentencing and Policy Advisory, Structured Sentencing, Rob Amberg, photographer (Box 10, Folder 108)
    5 contact sheets, 4 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1132H - Innovations 1997, State of Oklahoma, Department of Rehabilitative Services, Milestones Payment Program, Rex Fly, photographer (Box 10, Folder 109)
    12 contact sheets
  - 1132I - Innovations 1997, US Food and Drug Administration's "Reform of the US Drug Approval Process," Stan Schnier, photographer (Box 10, Folder 110)
    2 contact sheets, 2 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1132I - Innovations 1997, US Food and Drug Administration's "Reform of the US Drug Approval Process," Stan Schnier, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 338)
  - 1132J - Innovations 1997, Connect Care, Arkansas, John LeMay, photographer, 1997 October 10 (Box 10, Folder 111, Box 11, Folder 112)
    6 8x10 prints, 2 5x7 black and white photos, 93 3x5 black and white prints, 3 sets of negatives
  - 1132J - Innovations 1997, Connect Care, Arkansas, John LeMay, photographer - negatives, 1997 October 10 (Box 27, Folder 339)
  - 1132K - Innovations 1997, State of Alaska, Department of Community and Regulatory Affairs, Community Development Quota Program (Box 11, Folder 113)
    6 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1133 - Conference on Devolution, Boerne, Texas, Peace and Social Justice, Tommy Hultgren, photographer, 1997 September 10 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    7 contact sheets, 1 8x10 black and white print, 10 5x7 black and white prints
  - 1133 - Conference on Devolution, Boerne, Texas, Peace and Social Justice, Tommy Hultgren, photographer - negatives, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 340)
    7 sets of negatives
  - 1134 - Conference, Reaching Common Ground: A Day of Dialogue, Juliana Thomas, photographer, 1997 September 17 (Box 27, Folder 341)
    5 sets of negatives
  - 1135 - Conference, Strengthening Fragile Families Initiative, Juliana Thomas, photographer, 1997 September 17 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    2 8x10 color photos
  - 1135 - Conference, Strengthening Fragile Families Initiative, Juliana Thomas, photographer - negatives, 1997 September 17 (Box 27, Folder 342)
    6 sets of negatives